hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft we are
cruising our way through hermitville
where something quite drastic has
happened
can you see it
can you sit look at I
I don't know what it is
I'm not sure I want to know what it is
well at least you're gonna find out but
something's a bit weird today and I'm
not sure if you would notice immediately
because everything seems absolutely
Dandy but look what happens uh when I
hold something
[Laughter]
my skin is on backwards and I thought I
could have a little bit of fun at the
start of this episode messing with a
couple of the people online today they
have no idea I'm gonna go and see if I
can find them somewhere in the world and
see if I can trick them with this trick
that I demonstrated in my last videos
how to mess with your friends but let's
go and see if we can find some of them
and just freak them out a little bit see
what happens
I think the key here is not to be seen
before you go down because obviously if
I'm wearing my armor it's very very
obvious what I've done I need to be able
to walk backwards towards them to make
this work now I expect that stress is in
her castle somewhere okay she's probably
been alerted to to where I am I need
nothing in my hands at all and this is
how we're gonna go in so I'm gonna walk
in backwards I oh this is it's difficult
to drive this one so let's where's the
door over there this is a lot harder
than it looks because I don't know
what's in front of me at all if I follow
this down and I also don't know where
stress is either she was right here
somewhere ah there she is there she is
let's see if I could trick her
everything's normal here
and now
and she figured she figured it out
[Music]
I'm just don't worry don't mind me
stress I'm just laying I'm just laying
around I think I'm just gonna I think
I'm just gonna fall asleep here to be
honest
this is this is actually quite
comfortable
well I'll I'll be off then I'll be off
see where the door is
it's got to look absolutely hilarious
right let's see if we can find Ren
should really check where people are
before I go looking for them oh this is
easier oh this is so much easier okay
I'm such a fool I've been I've been
driving backwards the whole time well
I'm still walking backwards this is
really confusing but I've pressed F5
twice right this is me walking forwards
this is me walking backwards but it
looks exactly the same and I can
actually see where I'm going I'm such a
fool okay right now
I don't think Ren is here he must be at
his actual base now do I dare try and
fly
yeah flying backwards is not easy
[Laughter]
this is the stupidest thing I think I've
ever done
it just looks like I'm being dragged
along
oh my goodness okay we need to go and
find Ren wherever he is I don't know
exactly which way it is to the to the
island anymore oh this is this is the
stupidest thing
I've ever done and I've done a lot of
stupid things okay so we're gonna
backstroke glide into Ren's base maybe
he's around here somewhere he's there
he's that he's that now to take off any
indication and now we've just walked
forwards it's as easy as that although
I'm now stuck in here great so we just
walk backwards towards Ren now don't
fall for it I cannot punch him because
punching is behind me like this
he has no idea we're here talking of
weird skins
skin what the heck okay so I've just got
a backward skin on renza Ren's a rat
ran straight of a rat he's uh she'd be
calling himself Ren the rat now
oh he's gone up there how do I can't get
up there I can't get up there or the
game will be given away I can't Sprint
either well the game will also be given
away
okay is it time to reveal what's going
on here let's get real close let's get
real close to him he does he's just
showing me his face oh it's a little rat
cage right now Now's the Time
laughs he's trying to figure it out
[Laughter]
[Applause]
it's literally endless fun
oh he's been he's been fooled for about
two minutes now thinking that I'm just
looking at him
[Laughter]
I think both of us me and ren win weird
skin it's just it is really unsettling
if you're on the other side of this it's
really really unsettling
laughs
[Laughter]
oh man this is
uh it's so simple yet so genius at the
same time
Ren doesn't like it now where can I find
x i
Z Zuma on the server he's like oh there
he is he's there let's see if I can
now get him need nothing in my hands
foreign
hi nothing nothing to see here I need
you to pay attention to the ex I can't
get up on this level I need him to come
back I need him to come here otherwise
my whole cover's blown
I can't jump up here
oh no
oh no there's a hole
oh no that did not go to plan at all I
don't think he noticed
I don't think he noticed at all that
there was some X has just completely
ignored the fact that I'm on backwards
no I think I think X is totally
oblivious to this I don't know how it
really looks like you I'm I'm falling
I'm genuinely falling looks like I'm
gonna crash no
if I could make elytra invisible
this would look amazing
okay I think that that's enough
backwards fun for today so let's go back
to the village and check out the
monstrosity that scar made I was too
busy being backwards to take a look
at this whoa whoa whoa
oh my
goodness is it a what is is it a plant I
think it's a plant it's connected to the
plant but I can't help but think it
looks like a some sort of demonic frog
type thing oh my goodness it said
you could have made this look a bit more
friendly scar so this is a friendly
build off we're not here to scare people
oh my goodness so there's the boulder he
hasn't touched that but he's gone and
made a giant oh my word
he's got like a giant claw or like a
venomous thing it looks like a Venus
flytrap thing and it's it's spitting
acid and it's spit acid all the way up
into mumbo's rocket and spit acid on my
build
I think I'm gonna have to clean that up
otherwise it's gonna melt or maybe it
should just melt part of it as I clean
it up
I like this build to really tell a story
and the fact that this is corrosive that
that cannot be good for my build that
cannot be good for my build I don't even
know what to do how do you re honestly
this is a genuine question
how do you respond to this
is he even at the top as well is he
taller than Mike oh he is these eyes are
totally weightless let's do the number
check 196. oh if I remember correctly
I'm 195 and a half I am at 190 and he's
at one nine he's five blocks taller than
me
with his eyeballs
what do I do how do I respond I took
some time just think about how I could
retaliate to the giant plant
and these guys already done it this guy
has already retaliated this build off is
moving incredibly quickly I cannot keep
up so mumbo's rocket has now gone
because iskel has built a giant magnet
that dragged it back down and I can't
help but notice it's pointing directly
where my base should be so I can't help
but feel there's probably a plan in
place here to disturb what I'm going to
be doing not only that but he's
deflected the laser once more and sent
it right over to this eyeball so I had a
look earlier and I found this the
eyeball actually has fallen off the
plant and it's over here it's just
poking out of a tree and it looks really
weird but it's interesting because the
eyeball is actually the top of scars
build so in typical build of fashion we
need to get rid of this particular
eyeball and I've been trying to figure
out how and then I noticed this this is
still in the air and still theoretically
traveling so I'm thinking what we do is
we bounce it back right at that eyeball
the plant will then lose its sight and
then the plant will not be able to spit
acid at us anymore or in theory but I
also think that this I've left for so
long now it has to have consequences
let's get into a quick time lapse of the
retaliation that needs to occur here
thank goodness for the replay mod
because this is going to look a lot
nicer this way so the acid has melted
away coincidentally my least favorite
part of the build that random tower that
I couldn't get right so it has melted it
away and I've left some acid to kind of
show that off a little bit and then I've
gone and started to build my house even
taller than it already is and it's
really starting to get a little bit top
heavy I like to make parts of the build
a bit thicker than others so this bit is
going quite wide in comparison to some
of the other parts and at this point it
really looks like it should have fallen
over a long time ago but thankfully
because of the style it still works it
does take quite a lot of tweaking you
have to get the roof Style Just Right
and overall I think I've done that
pretty well I'm not going to detail it
today and I'll explain later on but what
we did say earlier was we noticed this
big bit of acid going in the air and
since the Rocket's gone I'm just going
to repel it with a giant baton or
badminton racket full of slime and then
I'm just going to add a few Flames
underneath I don't expect that slime
thing to remain there for very long at
all so I didn't spend too much time on
it I imagine it's going to get in the
way of Mumbo so I'm going to assume that
that can just be blown up and removed at
any point so let's pretend that I'm the
spit Boeing I bounce off of that and I
suddenly make my way over to the giant
plant which I believe is called scarra
and I then Melt Away its other eyeball
and I've basically transferred all of
those blocks over here so that this
makes sense at the moment this build off
has told an amazing story I can't wait
to see where it goes take a look at this
it's absolutely insane this build off is
really getting out of hand and that
looks precarious that looks like it
could actually fall down I haven't had
time to finish all the detailing I'm
afraid I'm gonna have to do that off
camera in the next couple of days but we
are a once again straight at the top
this oh look how sad look how sad this
looks now he looks a lot less
threatening without the eyes
between me and iskau this plant suddenly
seems a lot less scary so we've built up
we are now back on top we are leading
this build off although I am being
chased quite quite firmly by by Scar and
iska although I'm not sure what iscal's
plan is anymore I don't know how he's
going to build with this giant magnet
and Rocket involved it's a very
suspicious very very suspicious either
way I feel pretty confident that we can
make it to build height first that
really doesn't count as my base this
isn't my actual house in any way I just
used this to bounce it off you really
should be able to bounce sorry like you
just hit it and take damage that's kind
of lame I wish in Minecraft you you
could fly top speed
and it bounces off but unfortunately not
the case so I'm pretty happy I am pretty
happy we are back on top we have taken
out whatever this monstrosity is
and I think we've placed ourselves quite
high enough the person that is actually
most behind in all of this is sweet
mustache mumbo jumbo who has been
thoroughly Left Behind look at this he
needs to make a big play to make it back
he's like three leagues away look he
doesn't even go up to the top of the
balloon there so he's got to get oh
I think he's being left behind he's
gonna have to think of something very
smart to be able to get back up here so
let's head back into the old lands
because I've got some more work to do on
Sahara and this is going to sort of set
up what I want to do in my next episode
now that Sahara fully functions and
works and we've even had a few customers
let's see how many diamonds there are in
here
okay not so many but 29 diamonds isn't
bad isn't bad it's nowhere near what we
spent on the place but we're only just
getting started remember we don't have
all that much stock we are adding more
and more things very slowly we
definitely need some more golden carrots
in here looks like we're almost out and
then we need to get more items in here
so one of the things that I'm basically
tasked with because I'm not very good at
redstone
surprise shock I'm not very good at
Redstone so I'm not qualified to make
all the Farms because most of these
things come from farms like the Ice uh
the the beacons all of those stuff
they're farmable so I'm in charge of the
stuff that's not farmable so what we're
gonna go and do is a little bit of a
grind and we're gonna go and grab a lot
of gravel so that we can stock up Sahara
with said gravel and maybe even some
concrete and things like that so let's
let's get some gravel so this isn't
going to be the most exciting time lapse
and fortunately it's only going to last
about 20 more seconds so don't worry
about it at all but this is the sort of
thing that we have to do off camera all
the time maybe not to this extent
because I am basically removing every
gravel Block in this area this entire
Gravel Pit is now mine and this isn't
even half of it I only time lapsed a
small portion of it just to give you a
taste of what this is like so yeah we
dug some gravel
here we go look at all of this that's
how many shulker boxes 13. oh this one's
not full but most of these are full of
gravel which is quite a lot I think it
will take a long time to sell this much
gravel and some of this of course will
be used for concrete Etc this is the
boring part of making hermitcraft videos
you've got to do things like collect a
lot of gravel I spent about an hour and
a half just shoveling gravel yeah not
the best but it has to be done sometimes
and now it is so I can now transport all
of this over to the stock room so that
iscal can load it into the machine
because I don't know how to do all that
stuff
there we go so let's pop all of these in
there and that takes care of that so I
do want to start stocking a little
something something every single episode
if I can so I did say that all of this
would end up setting up what I want to
do in my next episode and unfortunately
I don't have time for it today however
getting all that gravel and getting all
the stock in our shop will allow me to
do that so what I want to work on next
episode is advertising in a big way I
want to advertise hashtag shop at Sahara
now in order to do that we're going to
have to stock things and there's things
that we we're not stocking that we
definitely could be one of those is all
of the things that are in mumbo's
farming area like all of the stuff over
here so obviously mumbo's got all of his
machines
it looks like he's got another one over
there this place is gonna be like just
an industrial Heartland or something
oh new Farm very unstable
please do not touch
hmm
I Really Wanna I Really Wanna press the
button
I know I shouldn't I shouldn't no I
shouldn't no no no no no
he did no I won't do it I won't I know I
I really want to I really want to
I pressed all of these buttons in my
other episode
no I'm not gonna do it but there's lots
of things here that we should be putting
in Sahara that just aren't there because
it takes a long time to load up so one
of the things that I'm going to do off
camera is transport all of this stuff in
glowstone form I'll craft it all up and
give it to iskau to load up so I can be
like a transportation person and we can
start selling some Redstone products I
could craft all of this Redstone Dust
into various things it could be very
very useful indeed so that would bring
Sahara's stock up to Max Capacity I'm
sorry I've got to check this out
no I don't
go for it I'll go for it oh no oh
no
I've been I've been mamboozled of this
like Bamboozled but Mumbo salt
I thought I was gonna die my heart my
little heart I thought I was going to
die then okay lesson learned lesson
learned okay Mumbo I I won't no no no
touching the buttons no more touching
the buttons okay
oh man no more touching the buttons
I apologize I apologize I'll just pop
that back oh he even made he did this in
glass so that I wouldn't oh my goodness
all right that's that's enough for me I
think that pretty much sums up my plans
for Sahara we're gonna stock it and then
next episode we are going to promote
Sahara in ways that I bet would surprise
you so I'm going to think of every way
possible to get Sahara on everybody's
radar showing that it is ready to be
shopped at because 28 diamonds or 30
diamonds roughly is it's a good start
but it's not Stacks and stacks of
diamonds which is you know what we're
really after but I don't blame it
because we're not stocking everything
that people need we need more carrots we
need more Rockets we need a lot of
everything and that's going to take a
lot of work
hopefully combined work and when I
assume we stock some logs and everything
like that people will start coming to
Sahara a bit more seriously but anyway
that's it from me everyone thank you
very much for watching I hope you
enjoyed this episode it was a lot of
messing around today especially with my
backwards skin but um do let me know in
the comments if that sort of thing was
enjoyable to watch because I don't
normally do stuff like that so anyway
thank you very much for watching and
good bye